A Guide to the Asia Society records FA110
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Exhibitions and Events, 1963-1999; 3
  - Gallery Files, 1
    - Nepal - Publicity, Exhibited: 1975 September-November (Box 228, Folder 2636)
    - Nepal - Opening: Private/Preview and Members, Exhibited: 1975 September-November (Box 228, Folder 2637)
    - Nepal - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, Exhibited: 1975 September-November (Box 228, Folder 2638)
    - Nepal - Catalogue: Correspondence, Exhibited: 1975 September-November (Box 228, Folder 2639)
    - Nepal - Acoustiguide Script, Exhibited: 1975 September-November (Box 228, Folder 2640)
    - Nepal - Loan Agreements, Exhibited: 1975 September-November (Box 229, Folder 2641)
    - Nepal - Circulation: General, Exhibited: 1975 September-November (Box 229, Folder 2642)
    - Nepal - Circulation to Los Angeles, Exhibited: 1975 September-November (Box 229, Folder 2643)
    - Nepal - Circulation to Seattle, Exhibited: 1975 September-November (Box 229, Folder 2644)
    - Nepal - Correspondence: General (domestic), Exhibited: 1975 September-November (Box 229, Folder 2645)
    - Nepal - Correspondence with lenders, Exhibited: 1975 September-November (Box 229, Folder 2646)
    - Photographs of the Himalayas House of Snows Fund Raising and Financial, Exhibited: 1978 March-April (Box 229, Folder 2647)
    - Photographs of the Himalayas House of the Snows Gen'l. Correspondence A to Z, Exhibited: 1978 March-April (Box 229, Folder 2648)
    - International Center of Photography, Exhibited: 1978 March-April (Box 229, Folder 2649)
    - Photographs of the Himalayas House of the Snows Publicity (photos), Exhibited: 1978 March-April (Box 229, Folder 2650)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Correspondence: General (foreign), Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 229, Folder 2651)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Correspondence: General (domestic), Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 229, Folder 2652)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Correspondence with Dean Frasche, Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 229, Folder 2653)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Correspondence with Bunka-Cho, Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 229, Folder 2654)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Correspondence Lenders, Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 229, Folder 2655)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Financing, Budget, Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 229, Folder 2656)
    - S.E. Asian Installation, Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 229, Folder 2657)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Lectures and Seminars, Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 229, Folder 2658)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics Acoustiguide Script, Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 229, Folder 2659)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Lists, Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 229, Folder 2660)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Loans refused or Withdrawn, Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 229, Folder 2661)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Opening: Private, Preview, Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 229, Folder 2662)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - (A.K), Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 229, Folder 2663)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Loan Agreement (L-Z), Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 230, Folder 2664)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Publicity, Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 230, Folder 2665)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Press Clippings (extra sets), Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 230, Folder 2666)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics Publications, Misc., Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 230, Folder 2667)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Packing and Shipping, Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 230, Folder 2668)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Circulation to Philadelphia, Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 230, Folder 2669)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Circulation: Honolulu, Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 230, Folder 2670)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Circulation - General, Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 230, Folder 2671)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 230, Folder 2672)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Catalogue: Correspondence, Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 230, Folder 2673)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Catalogue: Manuscript-Original, Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 230, Folder 2674)
    - Southeast Asian Ceramics - Circulation: St. Louis, Exhibited: 1972 February-April (Box 230, Folder 2675)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Catalogue Correspondence, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 230, Folder 2676)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Catalogue Bussiness Arrangements, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 230, Folder 2677)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Acoustigude Script, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 230, Folder 2678)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Circulation/General, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 230, Folder 2679)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Circulation Fort Worth, Texas, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 230, Folder 2680)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Circulation Seattle, Wash., Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 230, Folder 2681)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Circulation San Francisco, CA, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 230, Folder 2682)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Correspondence General Domestic, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 230, Folder 2683)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Correspondence with/Bunka-cho, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 230, Folder 2684)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Correspondence with Lenders, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 230, Folder 2685)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Correspondence with Porter McCray, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 230, Folder 2686)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Correspondence with Henry Trubner (Seattle), Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 230, Folder 2687)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Correspondence General Foreign, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 230, Folder 2688)
    - Chinese Ceramics: Curators, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 230, Folder 2689)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Financing/Budget, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 231, Folder 2690)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Insurance, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 231, Folder 2691)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Lectures, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 231, Folder 2692)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Lists, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 231, Folder 2693)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Loan Agreements, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 231, Folder 2694)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Packing Shipping, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 231, Folder 2695)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Opening Private Preview, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 231, Folder 2696)
    - Chinese Ceramics - Publicity, Exhibited: 1977 April-June (Box 231, Folder 2697)
    - Birds, Beasts - Acoustiguide Script and Audio-Visual Script, Exhibited: 1977 October-December (Box 231, Folder 2698)
    - Birds, Beasts - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, Exhibited: 1977 October-December (Box 231, Folder 2699)
    - Birds, Beasts - Correspondence with Lenders, Exhibited: 1977 October-December (Box 231, Folder 2700)
    - Birds, Beasts - Correspondence With Stern, Exhibited: 1977 October-December (Box 231, Folder 2701)
    - Birds, Beasts - Correspondence: General Domestic, Exhibited: 1977 October-December (Box 231, Folder 2702)
    - Birds, Beasts - Financing, Budget, Exhibited: 1977 October-December (Box 231, Folder 2703)
    - Birds, Beasts - Insurance, Exhibited: 1977 October-December (Box 231, Folder 2704)
    - Birds, Beasts - Installation, Exhibited: 1977 October-December (Box 231, Folder 2705)
    - Birds, Beasts - Lectures, Exhibited: 1977 October-December (Box 231, Folder 2706)
    - Birds, Beasts - Lists, Exhibited: 1977 October-December (Box 231, Folder 2707)
    - Birds, Beasts, Blossoms, Bugs, Exhibited: 1977 October-December (Box 231, Folder 2708)
    - Birds, Beasts - Loans Refused or Withdrawn, Exhibited: 1977 October-December (Box 231, Folder 2709)
    - Birds, Beasts - Objects and Conditions, Exhibited: 1977 October-December (Box 231, Folder 2710)
    - Birds, Beasts, Exhibited: 1977 October-December (Box 231, Folder 2711)
    - Birds, Beasts - Press Clippings: Extra Sets, Exhibited: 1977 October-December (Box 231, Folder 2712)
    - Birds, Beasts - Opening - Private, Preview, Exhibited: 1977 October-December (Box 231, Folder 2713)
    - Birds, Beasts - Publicity, Exhibited: 1977 October-December (Box 231, Folder 2714)
    - Birds, Beasts - Stern Memorial, Exhibited: 1977 October-December (Box 231, Folder 2715)
    - Sasanian - Catalogue Business Arrangements, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 231, Folder 2716)
    - Sasanian - Catalogue Correspondence, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 231, Folder 2717)
    - Sasanian - Empire Catalogues - Complimentary, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 231, Folder 2718)
    - Sasanian - A-V Script and Acoustiguide Script, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 231, Folder 2719)
    - Sasanian - Circulation - General, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 232, Folder 2720)
    - Sasanian - Circulation to Cleveland, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 232, Folder 2721)
    - Sasanian - Circulation to Dallas, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 232, Folder 2722)
    - Sasanian - Conditions - Receipts Forms, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 232, Folder 2723)
    - Sasanian - Correspondence General, foreign, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 232, Folder 2724)
    - Sasanian - Correspondence General, domestic, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 232, Folder 2725)
    - Sasanian - Correspondence with Prudence Harper, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 232, Folder 2726)
    - Sasanian - Loans Refused or withdrawn, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 232, Folder 2727)
    - Sasanian - Installation, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 232, Folder 2728)
    - Sasanian - Press Clippings (Extra Sets), Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 232, Folder 2729)
    - Sasanian - Loan Agreements, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 232, Folder 2730)
    - Sasanian - Lists, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 232, Folder 2731)
    - Sasanian - Lectures, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 232, Folder 2732)
    - Sasanian - Insurance, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 232, Folder 2733)
    - Sasanian - - Correspondence with Lenders, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 232, Folder 2734)
    - Sasanian - Opening Private, Preview, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 232, Folder 2735)
    - Imports - Exports, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 233, Folder 2736)
    - Sasanian - Packing and Shipping, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 233, Folder 2737)
    - Sasanian - Financing/Budget, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 233, Folder 2738)
    - Sasanian - Publicity, Exhibited: 1978 January-March (Box 233, Folder 2739)
    - (Indian Paint./Brit. Raj: Acoustiguide Script) Room for Wonder, Exhibited: 1978 April-June (Box 233, Folder 2740)
    - (Indian Paint./Brit. Raj: Catalogue: Correspondence) Room for Wonder, Exhibited: 1978 April-June (Box 233, Folder 2741)
    - (Indian Paint./Brit. Raj: Correspondence - Gen'l Dom./foreign) Room for Wonder, Exhibited: 1978 April-June (Box 233, Folder 2742)
    - (Indian Paint./Brit. Raj: Correspondence - A.F.A.) Room for Wonder, Exhibited: 1978 April-June (Box 233, Folder 2743)
    - (Indian Paint./Brit. Raj: Correspondence - S. Cary Welch) Room for Wonder, Exhibited: 1978 April-June (Box 233, Folder 2744)
    - Room for Wonder: Indian Ptngs. Education Prgm., Exhibited: 1978 April-June (Box 233, Folder 2745)
    - (Indian Paint./Brit. Raj: Lectures) Room for Wonder, Exhibited: 1978 April-June (Box 233, Folder 2746)
    - (Indian Paint./Brit. Raj: Financing/Budget) Room for Wonder, Exhibited: 1978 April-June (Box 233, Folder 2747)
    - Room for Wonder: Indian Ptngs. Films, Exhibited: 1978 April-June (Box 233, Folder 2748)
    - (Indian Paint./Brit. Raj: ) Room for Wonder Lists, Exhibited: 1978 April-June (Box 233, Folder 2749)
    - (Indian Paint/Brit. Raj:) Room for Wonder Opening: Private Preview, Exhibited: 1978 April-June (Box 233, Folder 2750)
    - (Indian Paint./Brit. Raj: Press Clippings: Extra Sets) Room For Wonder, Exhibited: 1978 April-June (Box 233, Folder 2751)
    - (Indian Paint./Brit. Raj: Publicity) Room for Wonder, Exhibited: 1978 April-June (Box 233, Folder 2752)
    - Chinese Photos - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 233, Folder 2753)
    - Chinese Photography - Acoustiguide Script and AV materials, Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 233, Folder 2754)
    - Chinese Photos - Circulation: General, Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 233, Folder 2755)
    - Chinese Photos - Circulation: Yale, Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 233, Folder 2756)
    - Chinese Photos: Correspondence with AFA, Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 233, Folder 2757)
    - Chinese Photos - Correspondence with Lenders, Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 233, Folder 2758)
    - Chinese Photos - Correspondence with Clark Worswick, Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 233, Folder 2759)
    - Chinese Photos - Correspondence - General (Domestic), Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 233, Folder 2760)
    - Chinese Photos - Correspondence - General (Foreign), Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 233, Folder 2761)
    - Chinese Photos - Film, Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 233, Folder 2762)
    - Chinese Photos- Financing, Budget, Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 233, Folder 2763)
    - Chinese Photos - Installation, Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 233, Folder 2764)
    - Chinese Photos - Lists, Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 233, Folder 2765)
    - Chinese Photos - Loans Agreements, Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 233, Folder 2766)
    - Chinese Photos - Openings: Private, Members, Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 233, Folder 2767)
    - Chinese Photography - Objects and Conditions and Receipts, Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 233, Folder 2768)
    - Chinese Photos - Packing, Shipping (imports-exports), Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 233, Folder 2769)
    - Chinese Photos - Press Clippings (Extra set), Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 234, Folder 2770)
    - Chinese Photos - Publicity, Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 234, Folder 2771)
    - Photos of China - Poster, Exhibited: 1978 June-August (Box 234, Folder 2772)
    - Gupta - Catalogue - Business Arrangements, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 234, Folder 2773)
    - Gupta - Acoustiguide Correspondence, Audiovisual and film inquiries, Correspondence, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 234, Folder 2774)
    - The Ideal Image: The Gupta - Sculptural Tradition, etc., Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 234, Folder 2775)
    - Gupta - Catalogue - Correspondence complimentary copy requests, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 234, Folder 2776)
    - Gupta - Circulation: General, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 234, Folder 2777)
    - Gupta - Circulation to Chicago, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 234, Folder 2778)
    - Gupta - Correspondence: General Domestic, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 234, Folder 2779)
    - Gupta - Circulation to fort worth, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 234, Folder 2780)
    - Gupta - Correspondence with Dr. Pal, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 234, Folder 2781)
    - Gupta - Correspondence: General Foreign, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 234, Folder 2782)
    - Gupta - Correspondence with Lenders, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 235, Folder 2783)
    - Gupta - Financing, Budget, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 235, Folder 2784)
    - Gupta - Insurance, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 235, Folder 2785)
    - Gupta - Lectures, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 235, Folder 2786)
    - Gupta - Lists, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 235, Folder 2787)
    - The Ideal Image: Gupta - Sculpture, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 235, Folder 2788)
    - Gupta - Films, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 235, Folder 2789)
    - Gupta - Lectures Correspondence, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 235, Folder 2790)
    - The Ideal Image: Gupta - Loans withdrawn or refused, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 235, Folder 2791)
    - Gupta - Packing and Shipping (with section for imports-exports), Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 235, Folder 2792)
    - Gupta - Imports/Exports, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 235, Folder 2793)
    - Gupta - Sculptural Tradition - Objects and Conditions and Receipts, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 235, Folder 2794)
    - Gupta - Opening - Private, Preview, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 235, Folder 2795)
    - Gupta - Press Clippings (Extra Sets), Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 235, Folder 2796)
    - Gupta - Publicity, Exhibited: 1978 October-December (Box 236, Folder 2797)
    - It is written: Calligraphy in the arts of the muslim world, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 236, Folder 2798)
    - Calligraphy - Catalogue - Correspondence, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 236, Folder 2799)
    - Calligraphy - Circulation: Cincinnati, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 236, Folder 2800)
    - Calligraphy - in the arts of the muslim world: circulation: s. Louis, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 236, Folder 2801)
    - Calligraphy - Circulation to Seattle, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 236, Folder 2802)
    - Calligraphy - Correspondence with Lenders, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 236, Folder 2803)
    - Calligraphy - Loans Refused or withdrawn, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 236, Folder 2804)
    - Calligraphy - Circulation: General, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 236, Folder 2805)
    - Calligraphy - Lectures, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 236, Folder 2806)
    - Calligraphy - Front Desk Material, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 236, Folder 2807)
    - Calligraphy - Correspondence: General (Domestic), Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 236, Folder 2808)
    - Calligraphy - Loan Agreements, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 236, Folder 2809)
    - Calligraphy - Correspondence: General (foreign), Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 236, Folder 2810)
    - Calligraphy - Correspondence with Texas Press, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 236, Folder 2811)
    - Calligraphy - Correspondence with Translators, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 236, Folder 2812)
    - Calligraphy - Correspondence with A. Welch, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 237, Folder 2813)
    - Calligraphy - Financing, Budget, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 237, Folder 2814)
    - Calligraphy - Installation, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 237, Folder 2815)
    - Calligraphy - Insurance, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 237, Folder 2816)
    - Calligraphy - Lectures, Films, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 237, Folder 2817)
    - Calligraphy - Lists, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 237, Folder 2818)
    - Calligraphy - Opening: Private, Preview, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 237, Folder 2819)
    - Calligraphy - Press Clippings - Extra Sets, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 237, Folder 2820)
    - Calligraphy - Publicity, Exhibited: 1979 January-March (Box 237, Folder 2821)
    - The Grand Mogul - Imperial Painting in India 1600-1660, Exhibited: 1979 April-June (Box 237, Folder 2822)
    - Grand Mogul - Catalogue - Correspondence, Exhibited: 1979 April-June (Box 237, Folder 2823)
    - Grand Mogul - Correspondence General (Domestic), Exhibited: 1979 April-June (Box 237, Folder 2824)
    - Grand Mogul - Correspondence with Sterling and Francine Clark Inst., Exhibited: 1979 April-June (Box 237, Folder 2825)
    - Grand Mogul - Financing, Budget, Exhibited: 1979 April-June (Box 237, Folder 2826)
    - Grand Mogul - Installation, Exhibited: 1979 April-June (Box 237, Folder 2827)
    - Grand Mogul - Lists, Exhibited: 1979 April-June (Box 237, Folder 2828)
    - Grand Mogul - Lists, Exhibited: 1979 April-June (Box 237, Folder 2829)
    - The Grand Mogul - Publicity, Exhibited: 1979 April-June (Box 237, Folder 2830)
    - Grand Mogul - Opening Private, Members, Exhibited: 1979 April-June (Box 237, Folder 2831)
    - The Grand Mogul - Publicity (Extra sets), Exhibited: 1979 April-June (Box 237, Folder 2832)
    - Indonesian Textiles - Lecturers, Exhibited: 1979 July-September (Box 237, Folder 2833)
    - Indonesian Textiles - Publcity Clippings (extra sets), Exhibited: 1979 July-September (Box 237, Folder 2834)
    - Indonesian Textiles - Splendid symbols, Exhibited: 1979 July-September (Box 237, Folder 2835)
    - Indonesian Textiles - Receipts, Exhibited: 1979 July-September (Box 237, Folder 2836)
    - Indonesian Textiles - Education Program, Exhibited: 1979 July-September (Box 237, Folder 2837)
    - Indonesian Textiles - Correspondence With Textile Mus., Exhibited: 1979 July-September (Box 237, Folder 2838)
    - Indonesian Textiles - Financing, Budget, Exhibited: 1979 July-September (Box 237, Folder 2839)
    - Indonesian Textiles - Lists, Exhibited: 1979 July-September (Box 237, Folder 2840)
    - Indonesian Textiles - Opening, Exhibited: 1979 July-September (Box 238, Folder 2841)
    - Indonesian Textiles - Publicity, Exhibited: 1979 July-September (Box 238, Folder 2842)
    - Indonesian Textiles - Packing and Shipping, Exhibited: 1979 July-September (Box 238, Folder 2843)
    - Master w. jap. Budddhist ptgs. - Acoustiguide Script, Exhibited: 1979 October-December (Box 238, Folder 2844)
    - Masterw. Jap. Buddhist ptgs.: Lectures, Exhibited: 1979 October-December (Box 238, Folder 2845)
    - Masterw. Jap. Buddhist ptgs.: Installation, Exhibited: 1979 October-December (Box 238, Folder 2846)
    - Masterw. Jap. Buddhist ptgs.: Insurance, Exhibited: 1979 October-December (Box 238, Folder 2847)
    - Masterw. Jap. Buddhist ptgs.: Correspondence with Lenders, Exhibited: 1979 October-December (Box 238, Folder 2848)
    - Masterw. Jap. Buddhist ptgs.: Financing/Budget, Exhibited: 1979 October-December (Box 238, Folder 2849)
    - Masterw. Jap. Buddhist ptgs.: circulation to Denver, Exhibited: 1979 October-December (Box 238, Folder 2850)
    - Masterw. Jap. Buddhist ptgs.: Correspondence: General, domest., Exhibited: 1979 October-December (Box 238, Folder 2851)
    - Masterw. Jap. Buddhist ptgs.: Correspondence-John Rosenfield and ten Grotenhvis, Exhibited: 1979 October-December (Box 238, Folder 2852)
    - Masterw. Jap. Buddhist ptgs.: Correspondence: General, foreign, Exhibited: 1979 October-December (Box 238, Folder 2853)
    - Masterw. Jap. Buddhist ptgs.: Circulation: General, Exhibited: 1979 October-December (Box 238, Folder 2854)
    - Masterw. Jap. Buddhtst ptgs.: Press Clippings: Extra Sets, Exhibited: 1979 October-December (Box 238, Folder 2855)
    - Masterw. Jap. Buddhist ptgs.: Packing and Shipping Conditions, Exhibited: 1979 October-December (Box 238, Folder 2856)
    - Masterw. Jap. Buddhist ptgs.: Publicity, Exhibited: 1979 October-December (Box 238, Folder 2857)
    - Masterw. Jap. Buddhist ptgs.: Lists, Exhibited: 1979 October-December (Box 238, Folder 2858)
    - Masterw. Jap. Buddhist ptgs.: Opening: Private/Preview, Exhibited: 1979 October-December (Box 238, Folder 2859)
    - Masterw. Jap. Buddhist ptgs.: Loans Refused or Withdrawn, Exhibited: 1979 October-December (Box 238, Folder 2860)
    - Masterw. Jap. Budd. Painting: Correspondence W. Fontein, Exhibited: 1979 October-December (Box 238, Folder 2861)
    - Two Rooms - Brochure, undated (Box 238, Folder 2862)
    - Two Rooms - Correspondence with Virginia Field, undated (Box 238, Folder 2863)
    - Two Rooms - Installation, undated (Box 238, Folder 2864)
    - Two Rooms - Publcity, undated (Box 238, Folder 2865)
    - Guimet - Acoustiguide Script (Box 238, Folder 2866)
    - Guimet - Catalogue: Business Arrangements (Box 238, Folder 2867)
    - Guimet - Catalogue - Correspondence (Box 238, Folder 2868)
    - Guimet - Conditions (Box 238, Folder 2869)
    - Guimet Contract (Box 238, Folder 2870)
    - Guimet - Correspondence with French Government (Box 238, Folder 2871)
    - Guimet - Circulation: General (Box 238, Folder 2872)